CHRISTIAN SMITH

Web Developer

Phone: 07949820414

Email: smithchristian4@hotmail. com

Website: www.christiancodes.co. uk

Github: www.github.com/ aines25

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/ smithchristian4

Location: Crewe / London

Interests:

- Cycling
- Fitness
- Gaming
- Self Development
- Football
- Travelling

Profile

Ex professional athlete & fitness professional over the last 18 years, aiming to transfer team and leadership skills experience gained over to the development world. As a self taught developer I am seeking a new challenge in the world of tech.

Experience

Freelance Web Developer 2020 - Present

- Learned the key principles of HTML, CSS & Javascript to create dynamic, mobile responsive websites across all devices.
- Implemented the use of Bootstrap in projects to aid with layout and mobile responsiveness.
- Use of version control and deployment of websites via GitHub & GitHub Pages.
- Ability to develop accurate representations of sites from a mock up design & problem solve errors within the code.

Fitness Manager / Personal Trainer, Bannatyne Health Club, 2013 - Present

- Responsible for the management of the fitness product at the branch, timetable & staff rota design and individual personal programs & classes to meet members goals.
- Responsible of the day to day running of the club in the absence of the General Manager.
- Responsible for delivery of training to the fitness team to continue their ongoing development.
- First port of call for any queries or issues regarding to fitness.

Professional & Semi-Professional Football Player, 2005-Present

First team player representing football clubs throughout the English football pyramid. Full time professional upon leaving school, I later transitioned to a part-time model.

Education

University of Somewhere, City, County - Degree, Year

Skills

- HTML / CSS / Javascript
- Bootstrap
- GitHub